

DEVELOPER/ANALYST/SUPERVISOR

Email: btsmith.go@gmail.com

Portfolio: www.btsmithportfolio.com

OBJECTIVE

I'm a self-taught developer who is passionate about making the world better though innovation. I'm also an analytical Inventory Supervisor successful in conducting audits of inventory records to ensure accuracy. My area of expertise is problem-solving and discovering solutions through deep analysis and technology.

EXPERIENCE

Value Merchandisers-Memphis, TN (2011-2023)

Inventory Supervisor | 10/2017-10/2023

- Managed inventory control software to provide inventory level updates and reordering notices.
- Conducted monthly inventories of materials on work floor.
- Led warehouse improvement initiatives to advance operational efficiencies.
- Tracked time spent on assignments each day for productivity reporting.
- Assisted and instructed semi-annual inventory audits.

Inventory Lead | 8/2016-10/2017

- Assisted with inventory daily operations such as cycle counting and evaluating systems reports.
- Lead team of cycle counters.

• Analyzed inventory reports with knowledge of Microsoft Excel and SQL.

Inventory Cycle Counter | 7/2012 - 8/2016

- Kept accurate record of inventory on hand.
- Utilized RF guns to update inventory records.

Module Supporter | 9/2011 - 7/2012

- Maintained and gathered products for order processing.
- Processed orders utilizing RF Equipment.
- Assisted order selectors in order processing.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration

University of Mississippi 2006-2010

Economics

Associates of Arts

Northwest Community College 2004-2006

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT
- REACT NATIVE
- NODEJS
- SQL

- MICROSOFT OFFICE
- TAILWINDCSS
- PLANNING AND ORGANIZING
- INVENTORY MANAGEMENT